{
"question": "一",
"answer": "いち"
},
{
"question": "お祖母さん",
"answer": "おばあさん"
},
{
"question": "涼しい",
"answer": "すずしい"
},
{
"question": "其方",
"answer": "そちら"
},
{
"question": "厚い",
"answer": "あつい"
},
{
"question": "お兄さん",
"answer": "おにいさん"
},
{
"question": "お姉さん",
"answer": "おねえさん"
},
{
"question": "汚い",
"answer": "きたない"
},
{
"question": "危ない",
"answer": "あぶない"
},
{
"question": "並べる",
"answer": "ならべる"
},
{
"question": "お腹",
"answer": "おなか"
},
{
"question": "不味い",
"answer": "まずい"
},
{
"question": "曇る",
"answer": "くもる"
},
{
"question": "ご飯",
"answer": "ごはん"
},
{
"question": "黄色い",
"answer": "きいろい"
},
{
"question": "お菓子",
"answer": "おかし"
},
{
"question": "磨く",
"answer": "みがく"
},
{
"question": "賑やか",
"answer": "にぎやか"
},
{
"question": "鳴く",
"answer": "なく"
},
{
"question": "夕飯",
"answer": "ゆうはん"
},
